[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the three astronauts from Apollo 11 has lost a child in 1962?", "correct_answer": "Neil Armstrong", "incorrect_answers": ["Both Collins and Armstrong", "Edwin Eugene Buzz Aldrin, Jr.", "Michael Collins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is proof that microbes existed on this planet.", "correct_answer": "Mars", "incorrect_answers": ["Pluto", "The Sun", "Neptune"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do foxes hibernate in winter?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which EU member state was known to the ancient Greeks and Romans as Dacia?", "correct_answer": "Romania", "incorrect_answers": ["Macedonia", "Bulgaria", "Slovenia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This very popular math term comes from the name of the man who wrote the first great algebra textbook.", "correct_answer": "algorithm", "incorrect_answers": ["algebra", "program", "graph"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These lines can be heard in what 1964 movie starring Sean Connery?\nMei-Lei: Can I do anything for you, Mr. Bond? \nJames Bond: Uh, just a drink. A martini, shaken, not stirred.", "correct_answer": "Goldfinger", "incorrect_answers": ["The Man with the Golden Gun", "Quantum of Solace", "Thunderball"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We all know that the formula of water is H2O but can you remember this important property of water: in the water molecule at what angle is each of the hydrogen atoms from the oxygen atom?", "correct_answer": "104.45 degrees", "incorrect_answers": ["180 degrees", "114.5 degrees", "90 degrees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Trans-fats are definitely unwholesome. Which of these foods is poorest in trans fatty acids?", "correct_answer": "sunflower oil", "incorrect_answers": ["margarine", "vegetable shortenings", "cookies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other common name is used to refer to the hairstyle known as a Croydon facelift?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Council house facelift", "Essex facelift", "Millie Facelift"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Golden State Warriors of the NBA once traded a player and a draft choice for center, Billy Joel Carroll.  Who were the two players they traded?", "correct_answer": "Robert Parrish and Kevin McHale", "incorrect_answers": ["Dennis Johnson and  JoJo White", "Rick Barry and Fred Hetzel", "Cliff Hagan and Easy Ed MCCauley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What vegetable is used for the preparation of the traditional Norwegian bread called Lefse?", "correct_answer": "Potato", "incorrect_answers": ["Pumpkin", "Beans", "Peas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Not accounting for daylight saving, what is the hour difference between Central Time Zone (CST) in America and Central European Time (CET)?", "correct_answer": "7 hours", "incorrect_answers": ["5 hours", "9 hours", "12 hours"]}]